Ayaka Miyake

London, UK

+44 7709-211-613

ayakamiyake7@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayaka-miyake/

https://github.com/ayakamiyake7

https://portfolio-ayakamiyake7.vercel.app/

About

Enthusiastic Front End Developer with skills in developing component-based responsive web applications using React, Next.js, Gatsby and Javascript. I also worked in Web Design as a web designer. I enjoy working with React.js. I am also passionate about design and using that in my components and successfully involved in both the front end and the design process with UI/UX.

Skills

React / Recoil / Next.js / Gatsby / JavaScript / jQuery / HTML / CSS / SCSS / Version Control / Web design / Figma / Adobe XD

Experience

Freelance Front End Developer - Argo, Inc. Remote Contract I 08. 2021 - Present

- · Helped clients develop services that were specific to their needs.
- · Instrumental in a team of 2 developers, reviewed code and helped provide additional perspective on the board process.
- · Created 3 landing pages in a week whlist organising the design process / SCSS single-handedly.

Web Assistant - Eikoku News Digest Ltd. London I 10. 2022 - Present

- · Designing and developing a website about immigration and accountant services from scratch using Gatsby/React.js.
- · Update websites using HTML/CSS.

Front End Developer - Argo, Inc. Nagoya, Japan I 04. 2019 - 09. 2020

- Tasked with the maintenance and updates to 10+ websites and provided person centred care to those clients.
- Took verbal instructions from clients and turned into design components such as contact form and buttons with 2 team members and satisfied clients with the outcome.
- · Developed frontend using JavaScript collaborating with backend teams to deliver projects.

Web Designer - Piece Craft, Inc. Nagoya, Japan I 04. 2018 - 03. 2019

- Re-designed the website to increase user engagement for the product and increased products purchases by 20% through the website.
- · Developed front-end using JavaScript with revised brand guidelines to reflect the new brand image with help of the team.
- · Collaborated with both clients and back-end teams to convert client specifications to fully functional products.

Civil Servant - Sekigahara Town Hall Gifu, Japan I 04. 2014 - 03. 2018

- Designed the layout of the town's monthly magazines to attract more readers.
- · Increased dramatically profits in my area of responsibility by more than sixfold through my actions and implemented business system.

Education

London College of Communication, UAL Online, London I 2020 - 2021

· Pre-degree, Certificate in Higher Education: Preparation for Design, Media and Screen

Kwansei Gakuin University Hyogo, Japan I 2010 - 2014

• Undergraduate Degree in Policy Studies focusing on Urban Planning and Regional Revitalisation